Moch. Dzawil Haiat

August, 30th 2000 | Central Jakarta, DKI Jakarta

087785381291 | mhaikal127@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/moch-dzawil-haiat/ | https://mdhaiat.vercel.app/

Personal Summary

I am a computer science graduate with experience in coding using the PHP programming language as well as the Laravel framework. I also have a sufficient understanding of Javascript, Vue JS, Bootstrap, and Tailwind CSS, which aids in creating appealing and responsive designs. I excel in teamwork, work diligently, uphold honesty, and possess an amiable personality.

Skills

Programming Vue and Node JS: Beginner

Skills Javascript: Moderate

PHP, HTML5, Laravel, CSS, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, MYSQL: Good

Personal Skills Adaptability, Teamwork, Hard Work, Honesty, Time Management

Indonesian: Native Language Skills

English: Beginner Level

Work Experience

> PT. Nose Herbal Indo (Jakarta Utara, DKI Jakarta) Web Developer (May 2022 - now)

- Build and maintenance a web company profile
- Build and maintenance a web application for reseller
- Build and maintenance a web application for recuitment
- Build and maintenance a web application for booking meeting room and vehicle operational
- Maintenance existing web application erp
- Troubleshooting printer, computer, and software
- > Hero Web Desain (Surabaya, Jawa Timur)

Freelancer Web Developer (February 2021 - December 2021)

- Build and maintenance a web application car rental
- Build and maintenance a web application online invitation

Experience Project

➤ 2022, Laravel

Rekruitment - PT. Nose Herbalindo Build a web applications for Recruitment for PT Nose Herbalindo. https://recruitment.nose.co.id/

➤ 2022, Laravel

Landing Page SateliteOfGlow – PT. Nose Herbalindo Build a Landing Page for Brand Satellite Of Glow. https://satelliteofglow.com/

➤ 2022, Laravel

Landing Page Satelite Of Glow – PT. Nose Herbalindo Build a Landing Page for Brand Satellite Of Glow.

https://reseller.satelliteofglow.com/

➤ 2022, Laravel

Booking - PT. Nose Herbalindo

Build a web applications for Booking meeting rooms and bookings vehicle operational for PT Nose Herbalindo.

https://booking.nose.co.id/

➤ 2023 - Ongoing, Laravel

Kos Boss House – PT. Nose Herbalindo

Re-Design Web Application Kos Boss House from PT Nose Herbalindo

https://kosbosshouse.com/

Education

➤ University of 17 August 1945 (2018-2022)

Bachelor's Degree of Informatics Engineering

• GPA 3.68

The award for Captivating Work by the Mass Media (2022)

Organization Experience

Captain of Food and Beverage (Sidoarjo, Jawa

Timur) Head of Discipline Commission (2019-2021)

- Arranging table settings according to standards and the preferences of clients or event management
- Memimpin dan mengawasi tim.
- Leading and supervising servers, bussers, and other staff involved in food and beverage service
- Coordinating all aspects of food and beverage service for events or catering services, including planning, preparation, and execution.

Memberikan Ijazah Kepada Awards this certificate to

Tempat dan Tanggal Lahir Place and Date of Birth

Nomor Pokok Mahasiswa/Tahun Masuk Student Registration Number/ Enrollment Year

Nomor Induk Kependudukan

Program Pendidikan Degree Program

Fakultas Faculty

Program Studi Study Program

Nomor Akreditasi Perguruan Tinggi University Accreditation Status

Nomor Akreditasi Program Studi Study Program Accreditation Status

Tanggal Kelulusan
Date of Conferment

Moch. Dzawil Haiat

: Surabaya, 30 Agustus 2000 Surabaya, August 30th, 2000

: 1461800109 / 2018

: 3578103008000006

: Sarjana (S1) Undergraduate

: Teknik

Engineering

Teknik Informatika
Informatics Engineering

: Terakreditasi Berdasarkan Keputusan BAN-PT No. 485/SK/BAN-PT/Akred/PT/XII/2018, 28 Desember 2018

**Accredited by the National Accreditation Board-Higher Education Decree No. 485/SK/BAN-PT/Akred/PT/XII/2018, December 28th, 2018

: Terakreditasi Berdasarkan Keputusan BAN-PT No. 12648/SK/BAN-PT/Ak-PPJ/S/XI/2021, 23 November 2021

Accredited by the National Accreditation Board-Higher Education Decree No.12648/SK/BAN-PT/Ak-PPJ/S/XI/2021, November 23rd, 2021

: 20 Januari 2022 January 20th, 2022

Ijazah ini diberikan setelah yang bersangkutan memenuhi semua persyaratan yang ditentukan, dan kepadanya dilimpahkan segala wewenang dan hak yang berhubungan dengan ijazah yang dimilikinya, serta berhak memakai gelar Sarjana Komputer (S.Kom.)

The bachelor's degree is awarded upon the fulfillment of all prescribed requirements, and the awardee is extended with all authority and rights appertaining to it, and the honors of academic title Bachelor of Computer Engineering

Rektor, Rector,

Prof. Dr. Mulyanto Nugroho, M.M., CMA., CPA.

NPP. 20220930308

Surabaya, 05 Maret 2022 Surabaya, March 5th, 2022 Dekan, Dean,

formo-or

Dr. Ir. Sajiyo, M.Kes. NPP. 20410900197

Piagam Penghargaan



REKTOR UNIVERSITAS 17 AGUSTUS 1945 SURABAYA

The Inspiring Figure Unitag

Memberikan Penghargaan Kepada:

Moch Dzawil Haiat

Wisudawan Program Studi Teknik Informatika, Fakultas Teknik Universitas 17 Agustus 1945 Surabaya yang telah berprestasi sebagai

SKRIPSI/TUGAS AKHIR MENARIK VERSI MEDIA
"Rancang Bangun Sistem Informasi Manajemen Kehadiran Karyawan Berbasis
Website dengan QR Code dan PHP Native pada Hero Web Desain"

Surabaya, 05 Maret 2022

Prof. Dr. Mulyanto Nugroho, MM., CMA., CPA

NPP: 22020.93.0308